The valuation
of this AI startup
from San Francisco
called Instinct
has just went from 100
million to 2.5 billion
dollars in just
the last few weeks.
They've raised around
350 million dollars
at this point
and the product is not
even public yet.
You have to be invited
to download.
The website's also super
mysterious
and
very, like, minimalistic.
And the founder is only
23 years old.
The product
is supposedly a personal
assistant that lives
on your computer
and can do things
like book flights
or make reservations
for you.
There are some users
that are concerned about
the amount of privacy
that you have to give up
because in order
to have the agent
just do everything
for
you,
you have to also give
it access to everything.
which will always
be sort of like mine.
Still one
of the craziest
evaluation jumps we've
seen, considering it's
still in private beta.